Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
We came out on To火anza
님
This is what wasatrained by a отсuerdo that he Berechanalik
We had no idea when we started.
We were a drama team
Actually, she was so inspiring man
Why am I here, right?
期待通りなどごめんなの自分でやれるからさ
どうだっていい理屈ばっか張り付いた
ハリボテの世界を生きてく
誰かのためじゃない 今はまだ自分に追いつくまで
かむしゃらでじめき飛ばした 体中の声が
翼広げて どんな未来も舞うよ
かぜうきて 自分を追い越すまで
フォンゼル promotionか
さおそろそろそろ
どっても会いばかり
彼に貴方を見た
うちしいぶりだ
彼は5ヶ月 sweetheart
Asta and Yuno had received their grimoires, but they had not yet set out for the Magic
Knight's entrance exam in the royal capital.
Asta was camping in the woods near Hajj village, diligently training with the sword he had
recently been given.
I have no idea what I'm doing, at all, I mean I've never trained with a sword before in
my life, I don't even know how I'm supposed to hold it, does hacking at trees really count
as training?
If I were you, kid, I would get out of the way and quickly, don't run right at me, hurry
and jump to the side, take that!
Very impressive, you took out that big guy in one blow, my mistake, I was doing some fishing
in the river and I guess I must have wandered into the boar's territory, ha ha ha, yeah,
anyway, name's Fonzal, I'm something of a nomad these days.
Nice to meet you.
Call me Zal.
Okay, I'm Asta from Hajj village.
It's a pleasure Asta, now tell me, are those yours?
Yeah, why do you want to know?
It's okay, I thought I was going to starve, I haven't eaten so much as a bite in two
whole days, never did catch any fish.
Awfully dense aren't they?
It's amazing how they just suck all the moisture right out of your mouth.
Yeah they do, so are you going to tell me why you're naked?
I didn't want to get wet while I was fishing.
What are these things?
You just ate them without knowing?
Some pot potatoes, a Hajj village specialty.
Cool.
Are you okay?
Here you go.
Yes, please.
Thank you.
What is this stuff?
It's got such a bitter taste.
It's my special Moguro leaf juice for increasing your magic power.
Well, I'm certainly feeling better.
If you don't mind coming to my house, maybe I can find a way to thank you for your help.
Your house?
Well, to be honest, I'm just kind of squatting there.
I never knew there were places this nice way out in the woods.
Every now and then you'll see one around.
Guess I should go ahead and get some clothes on.
Huh, a sword that can nullify magic.
That's new to me.
It's new to me too, but this baby is what's going to get me through the Magic Knights entrance exam.
That's why I've been holed up here in the mountains training.
Yeah, that's so?
What brings an old guy like you up here anyway?
Old guy, huh?
I'm actually only 28, thank you very much.
28?
No way!
Wow, you look so much older.
Right, let's just leave that there.
I'm waiting for someone.
Kind of a weird meeting spot.
It's complicated.
Okay.
So tell me, Asta, you're sleeping outside, right?
Why not stay with me while you're training instead?
Really? That'd be awesome, thanks!
Hold on, are you just after my pot potatoes?
Always treasure your encounters and connections with the people you meet.
True, they may not have a concrete form.
But those experiences will pile up in your heart and keep you company.
Are you kidding me?
This guy's obviously a total creep.
Are you actually going to stay with him?
Okay!
I think I'll take you up on that!
Thanks a lot, Mr. Zell!
Great!
Then let's talk about chores.
How are you at Chopin' Wood?
What?
Man, this doesn't seem to be working at all.
Well, maybe it's because all your weight is in your knees.
Huh?
The problem you've been having is that you can't manage a second blow once you swing your sword, right?
It throws off your balance.
Uh, yeah.
I know something that might help with that.
Keep your toes pointed in the same direction as your sword.
Then you take a half step forward with your right foot to shift your weight.
Go on, try.
Woohoo!
I did it, I can't believe I actually made it up to the second swing!
Ah yeah, you did it.
Pick it up pretty fast, too.
That was impressive.
No more pulling over!
That was amazing!
How'd you know that trick?
You fight with swords, too?
Well, no, not swords, exactly.
Hold on a sec.
Wind creation magic.
Emperor of slashing winds.
Whoa!
So cool!
You see, it's not a true sword,
but rather my magic taking on the shape of one.
It's the emperor of slashing winds.
I call it Slashy for short.
You're awesome at naming stuff, too?
Well, anyway, working with this thing
is how I picked up a little swordsmanship.
Hey, then can you teach me?
I'm sure anything you know will help.
I don't know.
Just a few lessons, that's all!
Please, I'll work hard!
Sure, no problem.
Sounds good.
It does, really?
Awesome, thank you so much!
Alright, yes!
I've got a teacher!
Oh, yeah!
Awesome! Awesome!
So cool!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
However, there's one thing I want you to promise me in return.
Asta, why are you working so hard to get stronger?
To become the Wizard King!
Ah.
I see. Well, that's good.
Yes, it's very good.
Wait, you're not gonna laugh?
No, why would I do that?
Because it's impossible or whatever?
But how can you know whether or not something is impossible until you give it a try?
Listen closely.
I want you to make me a promise, Asta,
that you'll only ever use what I teach you to make that dream come true.
Sure. What's that mean, though?
Just don't use what you learn here for evil. Use it to achieve your goals. Not as a tool for harming the innocent or bullying people.
I don't need anybody to tell me not to do that stuff.
So you promise?
Yeah, I promise.
Okay, then let's get to work.
Right! I'm ready whenever you are!
No! You're too slow!
Don't pause between hits. What we're after is rapid-fire attack.
Right!
You really are fantastic, Asta. Your defense and offense are both solid, and your footwork is improving, too.
What I don't understand is if you're this strong, then why didn't you just take care of that giant boar yourself?
Without either a sword or my grimoire on me, there wasn't a lot I could do. And besides, my skills with the sword aren't anything particularly advanced. You just seem to be especially good at putting them to use.
I don't know. I think it's because you're especially good at teaching them.
I think it's because you're especially good at teaching them.
I did do some teachery stuff once upon a time, so maybe.
Oh, really?
The students that I taught didn't think very much of me, though.
You know, I've had more than a hundred pupils.
But the way you're progressing, you might rank among the top three at least.
The top three?
Top two, maybe.
The highest ranked is kind of out there, not even using the sword as a sword, so I don't know if that really counts.
Well, anyway, even if you are accepted into a Magic Knight squad, I think you'll turn out to be a respectably skilled swordsman.
You really think so?
Then let's go! We've got some more training to do!
Whoa, not so fast. We aren't even done eating yet.
Several more days passed, until a visitor arrived.
I've returned, Master. Sorry it took so long.
Who's that?
You're back. So, what did you find out, Mariella?
Mariella?
One of my pupils. She's helping me. I've asked her to track down my fiancée.
That girl's your student?
If you need to find your fiancée, wouldn't it be better just to go out and look for her yourself?
The full explanation is a bit complicated, but I can't draw attention to myself right now.
I'm Asta from Hajj Village. The old man here is teaching me how to use the sword. Nice to meet you.
Please, this is no ordinary old man. While it might be true that he's old, he is an amazing old man.
So, look, I don't know who you are, but you should keep in mind that he is not the kind of old man that you can casually refer to as old man.
There are rules to follow for this sort of thing.
Like I told you, I'm Asta from Hajj Village, and I don't see what's so wrong about calling an old man, old man!
It's a simple matter of perception.
If you truly realized how amazing he was, you would be addressing him with the proper amount of respect and deference.
But when you say old man, it doesn't sound the least bit respectful or deferential.
How am I supposed to make the words old man sound respectful?
Maybe we could just let it go now, huh?
Listening to you two bicker isn't exactly doing wonders for my self-esteem.
So what about Dominante? Where is she?
Forgive me, Master. I don't know how to say this, but I believe it's possible that Domina has passed away.
Oh, no.
And so, Fonzel shared his story with Asta.
Fonzel and his fiancée, Dominante, had been members of the Diamond Kingdom's army.
No longer able to stomach the army's extreme methods, the couple plotted to desert but wound up separated as they sought to escape the kingdom's assassin.
Desperate to find his fiancée, Fonzel asked his former pupil and fellow deserter, Mariela, to search for her while he laid low.
Fonzel knew that when he made a move, the killer would, too.
Not wanting to endanger Domina if she were in hiding nearby, he was forced to go to ground in an abandoned house.
Wow.
Here's Domina's wand.
He was found where the assassin was thought to have attacked her.
That, and a great deal of blood.
I see.
If you'll excuse me, I need a moment to myself now.
Master, pardon me.
I'm sorry, but there's something I need to talk to you about.
Back when you helped me in the other students' escape, do you remember?
Yeah.
How's everyone doing these days?
Oh, wow.
That actually got a smile out of you.
You know, it's funny that you ask because everyone else but me is dead.
Huh?
They were murdered by the Diamond Kingdom's assassin.
Every last one of them.
What the hell are you doing?
This is my job now.
I do the kingdom's dirty work, provide it with useful intel, and dispose of its defectors when necessary.
If I hadn't agreed to cooperate with them, then I would be as dead as the others are now.
Don't worry, though.
We aren't going to kill you here.
I was given specific instructions to bring you back alive.
And in case you're thinking of trying to escape, you should know this building is surrounded.
That mage knight has entered the final stages.
We'll need your advice on finishing touches to ensure proper functionality.
That is where you were previously stationed, I believe.
It's Mars.
Sorry.
The boy has a name and it's Mars.
Stop talking about him like he's some kind of weapon.
All right.
Doesn't matter to me one way or another.
Are you okay?
And you!
What's your problem?
Aren't you grateful for what the old man's done for you?
Yes, I am.
I recognize that the combat techniques he taught me when I was his student are what's helped to keep me alive,
and for that he still has my respect.
If he didn't, why would I ever be concerned with the way in which you address him?
But then why would you do something like this?
If I fixated on those details, I could never get my job done.
So would you kindly not interfere?
I doubt you want to die for an old man you don't know.
I'd say that I know him pretty well by now!
No, Asta.
Please just listen to Mariela.
You have to get out of here.
You promised me.
You said you'd only ever use what I taught you about the sword to achieve your dream.
You shouldn't use your skills here in defense of some random old man, so get going.
I mean it.
Run!
Like I said, you're not just some random old man to me!
Hey, don't worry about it.
I may be old, but I can still handle these goons without your help.
You're already wounded!
I'll make my own promise.
I swear not to die at the hands of these diamond mages.
I'm gonna hold you to it!
No dying until I see you again!
You understand me?
Right.
I'm sorry, Asta.
This is for the best.
Domina.
Asta.
Please.
I don't care what happens.
There's no hope left in me.
No reason to go on.
I'm so very tired of all of this.
Just get out of here.
Leave me be.
No way!
A reason to live?
To keep going?
To hope?
Life doesn't just hand you those.
It takes work.
You have to fight to find them yourself.
If you're done moping, I could use a little help here.
Wind creation magic.
Emperor of slashing winds.
Winter wind.
That spell allows me to send out a lot of slashies at once.
I call it the Flying One.
Wow!
What an awesome name!
You saw me at a very ugly moment.
I'm feeling better now.
Don't worry.
Good.
Behind you.
He negated my spell?
What's wrong, old man?
Have you decided to give up after all?
We each get to choose for ourselves when the time has come to admit defeat.
And thanks to you, I realized that for me, that day isn't today.
There's no way I'm about to let this bunch of idiots end me now.
We're withdrawing.
Huh?
I'll bring up the rear.
Round up any casualties.
I want an orderly retreat.
You guys are just leaving?
When you're staging an attack, make sure to go in with at least three times the number of troops as your target.
If your number is halved, change tactics.
If halved again, retreat.
Or, so a certain instructor of mine told me once.
Don't think for a second that this is over, though.
I'll spend my whole life on your trail if I have to.
That's fine by me.
As of today, I've decided I'm done running.
From you, from myself, from anybody.
And I'm done being a coward.
Domina is out there somewhere alive.
I know she is.
I'll find her, no matter what.
So you just try to keep up.
You hear that, Mariela?
I hope you're ready to deal with his old man smell for the rest of your life!
Will you stop talking, please?
Words can wound.
I guess we'll both do our best, huh?
And, I think you might be learning the proper way to say old man.
Keep practicing.
Are you really leaving already?
Yeah, I'll keep looking for Domina no matter how long it takes.
When I finally have her, I'll try to find a way to atone for all the harm I've done in my life.
I haven't figured out exactly how I'll manage that yet, but considering my past, it'll probably take many years.
Which means, I won't be dying anytime soon.
You're the one I have to thank for giving me that resolve.
I'm just glad I could help.
I should get going, or it's going to get too hard to say goodbye.
See ya.
Right.
Hey, wait!
You're seriously going to leave just like that?
Sure am.
See, I'm a guy who likes to get things done.
I've been sitting around for too long, and now I'm ready to get to work.
Just like you should be doing.
Time's a-wasting.
What does that mean?
You're a guy who likes to get things done too, aren't you?
So get going.
There's no reason to wait.
You have everything you need to start making your dream come true.
Come on, now's when you decide to get all teacher-y on me, old man?
See ya!
Good luck!
Go become the Wizard King!
All right.
Guess I'll head back to the village.
Actually, I've got one last lesson for you.
Take this monster down, will you?
No way!
You can do it yourself!
And why are you naked this time?
Don't tell me you were fishing again!
I'll explain later!
Just help!
Stay away!
Let's get it!
Hey!
so
Where are you, my Domina?
I know you're still alive somewhere.
Uh, excuse me, miss? Can I ask you something?
Wait, please don't run away!
Just ignore the fact that I'm naked!